OK so regardless of
what system you're on,
you're going to want to open
up a terminal window now.
On Windows, that's the Git
Bash you've been working with.
On the Mac, you'll find
the terminal program
in the Utilities folder.
On a Linux system,
the terminal program
is usually pretty easy to find,
but can be in different places.
It doesn't matter which terminal
program you end up using,
the terminal is just an
interface to the Shell
and to other command
line programs that
will be running inside it.
Kind of like how your web
browser is an interface
to websites and services.
Now, pretty much
every terminal program
has a bunch of settings
that you can mess around
with to change the fonts,
and colors, and so on.
Now, we're not going to do a
lot of that in this course.
But do feel free to
adjust them to whatever
is comfortable for you.
Now something to
keep in mind, you
can have multiple
terminals open at once.
In fact, you can have any number
of terminals open at once.
Each one of them has its
own instance of the Shell--
a separate process
on your computer.
So if you happen to do
something in one terminal that
freezes or breaks it,
well, you can always
just use another one.
As you go through this
course, another thing
that will help you is to
look things up online.
There is a wealth of
information about the Unix
shell on the web.
If you're wondering
how to do something
or looking for a command that
you've never seen before,
use your favorite search engine.