So one of the cool
things about the shell
is there's always more to learn.
I've been using it
for 20 plus years
and there are still
features I've never
gotten around to using, and
people keep writing new ones,
too.
As you grow as a
developer, you'll
probably build up
a shell profile
that works well for
you, just as you
customized other development
tools such as your text editor.
Now there are a heck
of a lot of resources
on the web full of tips
and tricks about the shell.
Secret incantations
and general magic
for configuring and accelerating
your shell environment.
I've put just a few
of them on this page.
Now have fun with it,
and keep learning.