We've reached roughly the halfway point of this lesson,
and we want to check back in on your progress.
So far, you covered new ways to declare variables using let and const,
how to write template literals for easier string interpolation,
destructuring arrays and objects,
and some shorthand ways for initializing objects.
At this point, we hope you're starting to see how these improvements to
the JavaScript language will impact the way you write code moving forward.
The remainder of this lesson will focus on the addition of the for... of loop,
the rest parameter, and the spread operator.
However, before you move on,
there's one more thing we want to mention - iteration.
Iteration is a new mechanism for looping through data in ES6.
Understanding what iteration is and how it
works will be important for completing the rest of this lesson.