Promises are an interesting concept and solve
some tricky problems that we've had in previous versions of JavaScript.
Using a JavaScript Promise is the new way to handle asynchronous requests.
And just like most changes in ES6,
it's an improvement on the way we've structured code in the past.
Let's look at an example.
James here has been waiting patiently to take my order.
So if I say, "Hey,
can I get an ice cream sundae.".
Finally, I thought you'd never ask.
Great.
So I've made my request and he'll give me
this to represent that he'll return with something in the future.
But should I have to wait right here for him to come back and give it to me?
While he's making it can I get back to work on my next project?
Then when he's finished with the ice cream he
can notify me that it's ready and I can pick up where I left off.
Richard your sundae is ready.
Great.
Can I get some hot fudge,
some caramel, some whipped cream and cherry?
Sure.
Thanks.
Now I'm back to waiting again.
Going back and forth for making a request for
something than the downtime while that request is being fulfilled.
Being able to do work during that downtime and then being notified
that my request is finished is what Promises do for us in JavaScript.
It handles that "do this thing now" then
notify me when it's done so I can pick up where I left off.
Your sundae is ready.
Thanks.
It looks awesome. Here you Go.
Let's take a look at how you actually create and work with Promises.