Arrow functions are awesome and can really clean up your code by
removing a lot of the unnecessary things like the function keyword,
the return keyword, and curly braces.
Get those things out of here.
Yeah. Who needs those things? But don't just go
converting all of your regular functions in the arrow functions just yet,
because there's a big gotcha with the arrow functions.
The way arrow functions handle "this" keyword is different from regular functions.
Wow. Yeah, I mean that's kind of important to know about.
A bit more than kind of important.
In fact, the next section is all about
arrow functions and "this" keyword. Go check it out.