So here we are in a terminal.
Inside the terminal window,
we see a little message here,
and another message
here, and a cursor.
Now, this message
is the Shell prompt.
It usually displays some
information about the computer
you're logged into.
Exactly what
message you see here
will depend on your system.
Later on, we'll see
how to change it.
If you type something in at the
Shell prompt and press Enter,
the Shell will try
to run whatever
you typed as a command.
Throughout this course,
you'll be learning
a bunch of Shell commands.
Here's the first one.
The echo command is how we get
the Shell to print messages
back to us.
It's like console.log in
JavaScript or Print in Python.
Try it out.
OK, what happens if I
want the greeting to be
a little bit more enthusiastic?
Hello, shello followed
by two exclamation marks.
Huh, that's weird.
Hello, shello echo.
Hello, shello.
Hey, if I said that a
bunch of times in a row
that could be a number one jam.
Hello, shello echo.
Hello, shello.
The point being, there
are some characters
that have a special
meaning to the Shell.
The exclamation
mark is one of them.
If you're ever typing
something into the Shell
and it seems to be treating what
you're saying in a weird way,
all you usually need to do is
to put single quotes around it.
Huh, there we go.
That's a little bit
less repetitive.