So we just looked at Sets and WeakSets,
but I want to turn your attention towards Maps and WeakMaps.
Maps and WeakMaps, share a lot of things in common with Sets and WeakSets.
They both have similar properties and methods.
Maps and Sets are both iterable which means you can loop over them.
And WeakMaps and WeakSets don't prevent objects from being garbage collected.
However, Maps are unique because they're collections of key-value pairs,
whereas Sets are collections of unique values.
You could say that Sets are to arrays,
as Maps are to objects.
Yeah, that's good. In this next section,
we'll look at how you can create and use Maps and WeakMaps.