Now we know how to get files from off the web.
But what can we do with them once we have them?
Well, there's a shell command called cat
that just reads the file and outputs the contents.
Actually, it can read any number of files.
The name cat is short for Catenate
or Concatenate which means to run several things together.
So let's try that. Cat dictionary.txt.
Went straight to zucchinis and zwieback and zygote.
That's not very useful if we wanted to see the top of the file.
It just blasted the file at our terminal so quick that it went right to the end.
Fortunately, there's another program,
less, which shows us less of the file at once.
Specifically, it'll just show you one screenful of the file at a time.
You press space to scroll down or you can use the arrow keys.
It has some other commands like B to go back or slash to search.
When you're done in less,
you can press Q to quit.
And less is really handy.
It's used internally by a lot of other programs that might
sometimes need to display a lot of output and give you a chance to catch up.