When you look through your files in a graphical interface,
such as the Macintosh finder,
or the Windows file explorer,
a folder window shows you the files in
subdirectories in a particular folder or directory.
Like, here's the downloads directory in this computer for the downloads folder.
Directory in a folder are basically the same thing.
But in the shell, we'll use the word directory.
To list the contents of a directory in the shell,
we can use the command LS.
LS is a super shortened version of the word list.
When you start the shell,
it usually starts out looking at your home directory.
If you just run LS by itself,
it will print the contents of the current directory.
To list another directory, say,
Downloads, you can type LS followed by the name of that directory.
You can also change what directory the shell is looking at.
The command for this is CD,
which stands for Change Directory.
After you CD into a particular directory,
LS by itself will show the contents of that directory.
That's something you'll see a lot.
Many shell commands default to interacting with the current directory.
If you want to go back a directory,
you can do that with the special directory name dot dot,
which is also called the Parent Directory and
the semi-colon lets you write two commands on the same line.
The shell will just run them in order.