OK, so now maybe we've made a
bunch of files and directories
and stuff, and we want to clean
them up to delete some things.
Well, the Shell command
for deleting files
is rm, which is
short for remove.
rm works the same
as you'd probably
expect from other
Shell commands,
you just give it the name of the
file, or the names of the files
that you want to remove.
Now, I've got to give
you a safety warning.
In your GUI, you've probably
got a trash can or recycle bin
where files go when you
want to get rid of them,
but you can take them back
out if you change your mind.
The rm command does
not work like this.
It just removes the files.
If you want a
little more warning,
maybe you're afraid you
might remove a valuable file
by mistake, well, you
can use the option -I.
The I is for interactive,
which will prompt you
for every file it's
going to remove.
Now for directories, there's
a different command, which
is rmdir for remove directory.