Symbols are the latest addition to the list of
primitive data types available to us in JavaScript.
Previously, JavaScript only had numbers, strings,
booleans, null, and undefined as its primitives but now symbols have entered the mix.
James, what's a symbol?
Well, a symbol is just a unique identifier.
It's most often used to uniquely identify properties within an object.
For example, let's assume this ball is an object.
Richard, can you give me some fruit?
Sure.
Okay. So this apple,
and this orange, and this banana, to the bowl.
Now keep in mind, these fruits are also objects but now they're properties of this ball.
Now here's where things get interesting.
Can you hand me another banana?
So if I add this banana to the bowl,
can you see what the problem is?
Richard, hand me a banana from the bowl.
Which one?
Exactly. I need a way to uniquely identify this banana, from this banana.
In code, I can do something like represent this banana,
as banana one and this banana, as banana two.
But what happens when I keep adding more bananas to the bowl?
I think you see where we're going with this.
Thankfully, with the addition of symbols in ES6, we've got a solution.