OK.
So much for listing your files.
How about moving them around?
Here, I've got this
documents directory
with a whole bunch of files
in it and kind of a big mess.
I'd like to make
some subdirectories
and get things organized.
Now, in the GUI,
I'd need to do a lot
of dragging and dropping and
making new folders and so on.
But in the shell, I can do it
with just a couple of commands.
The first command I'll
use is MKDIR, which
stands for make directory.
I've downloaded a bunch
of books as epub files,
so I'll make a directory
called Documents
slash books to move them into.
Now I could cd into the
Documents directory first,
but I don't have to.
I can just make that
directory from here.
And you can see that when
I make it from the shell,
it shows up in the
graphical interface as well.
Next, I'll move the epub
files into that directory.
The command for moving things
is MV, which is short for move.
I have to tell it
two things, where
I want to move something from
and where I want to move it to.
Now, I could do these
all individually,
but we just saw that we
can use a star instead.
So I'll use MV for move
documents slash star
dot epub documents slash books.
What is that thing or what are
the things that I want to move,
and where do I want
to move them to?
And now if I LS documents
slash books, or open it up,
there they are.