You've seen how
many Shell commands
can be given the name of
a file or a directory,
like ls and cd can.
But that's not the only thing
you can tell a Shell command.
Many of them also support
options, or flags,
or parameters that turn on extra
behavior or special features.
Here's an example, ls-l--
the -l is an option to ls.
You can also use it along
with the name of a directory,
like this.
And what it does is to print out
a longer more detailed listing
of files.
The l is for long.
Try it out yourself and see
what you can find in it.
Here's something else you
can try along with it.
The Shell lets you match
filenames with a pattern.
Let's say you want to
list all the PDF documents
in your Documents directory.
The way to do this is
with a star, like this--
ls-l Documents/*.pdf.
The Shell turns the
star into a list
of all of the files whose
names match that pattern.
In this case, that's all of
the files whose file names end
in .pdf.