Remember that a polyfill is used to fill a hole
in a browser that doesn't yet support the native feature.
This polyfill start to check to see if the native startsWith method actually exists.
Why? Because if it does exist then
we don't want to override the native version with this one.
So if it doesn't exist,
then the browser running this polyfill will then run all of this code.
This adds a new method to Strings.prototype object.
The function defaults to the position indicated by
the second argument that's passed in or it'll be the first character of the string.
Then it just returns true or false.
If the string that's passed in is the same as the string that we're looking at.